# SHUBHAM DUBEY

**TECHNOLOGY ANALYST** 

Pune, Maharashtra.+9197306 36429mr.shubham54@gmail.com

Technology Analyst with experience of cross-functional teams in the development, documentation and delivery of process innovations driving the attainment of business goals. Seek opportunities to transform company practices into fresh, cost- effective solutions leading to more efficient operations.

### **KEY SKILLS**

COMMUNICATION



CUSTOMER MANAGEMENT



OFFICE 365



LEADERSHIP



**ADAPTIBILITY** 



**DECISION MAKING** 



**BUSINESS ACUMEN** 



#### **EXPERIENCE**

Infosys Limited -Feb 2020 - Present

- Handled five sub projects for an account related to PowerApps and Power Automate (MS Flow).
- Developed Multi-Lingual PowerApps for customer to enable 30k+ users to generate passes in times of Covid.
- Created and maintained PowerApps and Power Automate for Client to automate site storage increase functionality.
- Developed Microsoft Form and Dynamics 365 as per the business needs.
- Continuously taking ownership of all the enhancements in the already developed projects.
- Error-Free Implementation of my PowerApps with 100 percent efficacy.
- Requirement Gathering and end to end development of PowerApps forms and Power Automate (MSflows.)
- Documentation for user requirements, process flows and use cases.

Tata Consultancy Services Limited - Sep 2017- Jan 2020

- Analyzed user requirements, performed impact analysis and generated system requirements documents
- Collaborated with the project team in solution development and implementation; presented the business solution to the client
- Prioritizing competing demands from stakeholders and driving requirements from analysis through production with minimal support
- Analyzing existing customer satisfaction functionality requests for providing business-value based recommendations to Product Owners
- Translate stakeholder requirements into different deliverables such as functional specifications, user cases, user stories, workflows.
- Communicate client's business requirements by constructing easy to understand data and process models.
- Draft and maintain business requirement documents and align them with functional and technical requirements
- Partnering with Development Leads to identify opportunities for better collaboration and process improvements

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

#### **Date of Birth**

30 Nov 1995

### **STRENGTHS**

- Sagacious and Gregarious
- Buoyant, sturdy, and ability to handle different learning curves
- Acumen and efficacious
- Oratory.

#### **SKILLS**

- CustomerRelationship Management
- Business analysis and Requirements Gathering
- Project Management
- System Design and Team Management
- Risk Management, Impact and Gap analysis

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- SharePoint Online, PowerApps , Power Automate, Admin Center
- Microsoft teams, Power BI
- Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Jquery, Javascript
- Microsoft Office

# **EDUCATION**

Prof. Ram Meghe Institute of Technology and Research,

Amravati, Maharashtra 2013-2017 CGPA 8.01

**Bachelor in Computer** 

**Science and Engineering** 

V.M.V College Nagpur

2011-2013

Higher Secondary 68.83 %

Saraswat Public School

2010-2011

**Secondary Education** 

88.91%

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Certified Foundation level Business Analyst.
- Received multiple customer appreciation throughout the working duration
- Have been nominated by the team for my consistent and on time deliverables